<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AptronTute</string>
    <string name="history">Android Inc. was a Californian company created in 2003, the result of a joint venture between these four men: Andy Rubin (who spent 3 years at Apple as a software engineer between 1989 and 1992, Nick Sears, Chris White and Rich Miner who joins them in early 2004. At the beginning, the intention was to develop an advanced operating system for digital cameras and as the development was progressing it became obvious that their original target was restrictive and they concentrated instead on developing a new operating system to compete with Symbian and Windows Mobile (not to be confused with Windows Phone), both overtaken by iOS and Android since 2010 and pretty much discontinued.According to Adrianne Jeffries: “There has been speculation over whether Android is called “Android” because it sounds like “Andy.” Actually, Android is Andy Rubin — co-workers at Apple gave him the nickname back in 1989 because of his love for robots. Android.com was Rubin’s personal website until 2008.
             "The start of Android Inc. was shaky and the company had to be rescued financially on several occasions by Steve Perlman, despite their best effort their business model didn’t attract because the carriers (i.e. TalkTalk, Vodaphone, EE…) refused to give up control of the industry: the plan was to give the software for free to the manufacturers (i.e. Nokia, Samsung, LG, HTC…), then the carriers would order the models and customise/brand/modify the software and sell it on; Android would make their money by selling “value-added-services” on top to the carriers");
             </string>
    <string name="lesson1">
        UI DESIGN:
       1) Manifest file=A autogenerated file which contains all the information about the application.
        2)Toast= It is a class which helps us to broadcast a specific messege for some specific client.
       3) Activity=It contains View group which contains the views.
       4) View Group=It is a object which helps to arrange diffrent componets in diffrent manner.
         </string>
    <string name="lesson2">
        1) Text View:
        This class is used to display text on the android application screen. It also allows user to optionally edit it. Although it contains text editing operations, the basic class does not allow editing, So Edit Text class is included to do so.
2) Edit Text:
This class makes text to be editable in Android application. It helps in building the data interface taken from any user, also contains certain features through which we can hide the data which are confidential.
 3)Image view:
Image view helps to display images in an android application. Any image can be selected, we just have to paste our image in a drawable folder from where we can access it. For example: In below Code “@drawable/ic_laucher” has been taken.
 4)Check Box:
Checkbox is used in that applications where we have to select one option from multiple provided. Checkbox is mainly used when 2 or more options are present.
 5)Radio Button:
Radio button is like checkbox, but there is slight difference between them. Radio button is a  two-states button that can be either checked or unchecked.
  6)Button View:
This class is used to create a button on an application screen. Buttons are very helpful in getting into a content. Android button represents a clickable push-button widget.
7)Image Button View:
Image button is a button but it carries an image on it. We can put an image or a certain text on it and when we click it provides the operations assigned to it.


    </string>
</resources>
